Kostadis Roussos: Hello?
Wade Brown: Wake up Kostadis.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Very much right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just make sure I did this, I think I did it.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, by the way, I'm reading that book you recommended.
Wade Brown: The 20-odd words that created the internet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Wade Brown: Huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, that one.
Wade Brown: Yeah, isn't it dry as fuck?
Kostadis Roussos: It's actually… well, I mean, I wouldn't say it's dry as fuck, but it is really good.
Wade Brown: Yeah, no, it's super interesting, but it's super dry, like…
Kostadis Roussos: something? I guess… I guess we're… okay, so I don't know what you mean by dry, maybe that's the problem, I don't…
Wade Brown: I mean, it's not…
Wade Brown: it's got, you know, no interesting prose or, you know, storyline to speak of. I mean, it's just a long-form Wikipedia article, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh yes, yes, in that sense, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. It reads very much like something a lawyer would write.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I mean, and it is, right? Like, I think it actually is from very.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's a lawyer. No, the author's a lawyer, he makes that point quite clear.
Wade Brown: Has does his prose.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh my god, it's bros. Yeah.
Wade Brown: But it's super interesting to me, because it's just… it's crazy, all the stuff that went into the, the history of Section 230.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, and what's really interesting, I guess, from my perspective, is the fact that the book Like…
Kostadis Roussos: So there's this, like, meme on Facebook, right? Among social media, especially some people whom I follow on social media. They'll go, well, you know, there's no big company, no big internet companies in Europe.
Kostadis Roussos: And I'm like, yeah, but there's no big internet companies in Europe that just got sued by the federal government for harming young girls.
Wade Brown: Okay, but… We can always make more young girls.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: You do realize, yes, young girls, right?
Wade Brown: I'm… I'm… I'm terrible.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, if it wasn't for the fact that we know who you are, we would be offended.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: No, I, you know, I am a fan of move fast and break shit, you know? I don't like stagnation.
Kostadis Roussos: This is not a statement. This is actually not a statement of one is better than the other.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: There is an… there was an explicit trade-off made.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Like, you could say that the trade-off was literally that one. In Europe, they decided that they would rather… they valued collective… let's call it certain… they valued different things, and so they had different outcomes.
Wade Brown: Yeah, of course. I mean, that's… that's absolutely true. It's what you prioritize for.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, here's it.
Kostadis Roussos: Here's the summary of events according to Brewbarry.
Wade Brown: Brewbarry, who's not with us today.
Wade Brown: Of course, we're also missing a, Vukradin.
Wade Brown: Oh, didn't he… did he say he wasn't gonna make it this week? I forget.
Kostadis Roussos: Something…
Wade Brown: I don't take notes.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think… I don't see anything there.
Wade Brown: No, I thought he might have mentioned it in session, that's…
Kostadis Roussos: I didn't see anything like that.
Wade Brown: Pardon.
Wade Brown: One of these days, I'll stop being an old man, going to bed at 9.
Gary Young: And Eula instead.
Gary Young: Go to your coffin that minute.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Gary Young: I did not make a funny picture, yet for this session.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, damn it.
Wade Brown: What do we pay you for?
Kostadis Roussos: Tortle runs the board laid bare, cooks better than anyone I have eaten from. Soma's friend for years. Her preferences never moved while the rest of the city doubled, and that is because her supplier was never on the manifold in the first place.
Kostadis Roussos: I went into her kitchen with a halberd in one arm and the dragon sword in the other in a story about needing a delivery partner. The story did not work.
Gary Young: I'm getting inspired now.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Petra was booking a man to play Vukradin song under our band name every night.
Kostadis Roussos: She'd always disclosed it, was not him, and she made money off him anyway.
Wade Brown: He says, you gotta send these out earlier than, you know, 5 minutes into the session.
Kostadis Roussos: I know, I know, I know. I'm sorry, I thought I had done that.
Wade Brown: I'm just looking, it's like, Jesus, there's a lot here to scroll through, and I'm like, I want to read it. Like, I just would have read it, you know, 30 minutes ago.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, no, it was my bad, I felt bad, I thought I had sent it, yeah.
Wade Brown: That's okay, I am just… Hey, you know, you're a service top, it's fine.
Wade Brown: Anyway, you'll figure out what, you know, where Section 230
Wade Brown: you know, got tested weirdly. I love all the crazy history about, like, how it was used, you know, it's basically, we gotta treat this like a bookstore, like a bookstore can't be held liable for everything.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, I mean, it's very fascinating to see how a set of decisions produced a set of outcomes.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Wade Brown: And what's even more is the Telecommunications Decency Act had a lot of shit in it, and…
Wade Brown: They all got paired back, like, the only thing that survived is, like, the 26 words that are worth keeping.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, it's almost like the Anti-Communications Decency Act, or maybe the Wade-approved version of the Communications Decency Act.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it's crazy.
Gary Young: Greeson, while we're talking about Section 230?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, wait… well, you're no longer employed by Google, so you don't have to worry about legal consequences, but the reason we're talking…
Kostadis Roussos: The reason we're talking about it is because Wade recommended a book called The 26 Words That Changed the Internet.
Wade Brown: Created.
Gary Young: Okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And… and I thought it was… and I was telling him that I was reading it, and it's a superb book.
Wade Brown: It is. It's… I've never found anything like it. I've tried, like, I… I don't know what it is about it, but it's just fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me send a note to Dave, I don't know whether he's joining us.
Gary Young: 26 words is the name of the book.
Wade Brown: 26 words that created the internet, and it's just, like, 200 pages on Section 230. 200 pages on 26 words.
Kostadis Roussos: And it's a series of legal cases.
Kostadis Roussos: Essentially, it's… it describes the origin of the law, right, where the law started.
Kostadis Roussos: It describes how the law came into existence, the set of legal challenges that were made against the laws.
Kostadis Roussos: And how those laws… those laws affect… how… how they… how they evolved over time.
Kostadis Roussos: And it explains…
Gary Young: Intimidated by legal stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Gary Young: I'm not intimidated by legal stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, it's not…
Wade Brown: It's not intimidating, it's very approachable.
Gary Young: No, this is, you know, life. That is a feature of me.
Wade Brown: Yeah, but it's a very easy, very easy read for how deep it goes into detail. Like, I keep joking it's a long-form Wikipedia.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's very well written.
Gary Young: I was reading, Don't Be Evil, I will say,
Gary Young: it is a little bit less about Google, more about Technology companies, in general?
Gary Young: And about her dating life.
Wade Brown: Hurricane?
Kostadis Roussos: Anywhere.
Gary Young: Claire Steepleton.
Gary Young: So, this is a book by a… someone I knew at Google, that was talking about her… experience.
Gary Young: called Don't be Evil, and it is,
Gary Young: Yeah, it's been going around the circuit lately.
Gary Young: But…
Gary Young: I will say that, there's a whole lot more dating, office dating, going on than I had been aware of.
Wade Brown: I mean, you're not supposed to be aware of it, unless you're a tremendous gossip.
Wade Brown: His name is Bimbo.
Wade Brown: I don't know why you keep writing Bimble in here.
Wade Brown: Hi, Dave!
David Mendenhall: Stephane's out today.
Wade Brown: Yeah, he said he's got, I don't know, something.
Kostadis Roussos: He claimed he had some issue, you know.
Wade Brown: Actually, he didn't even say why, he just said no, which is fine.
David Mendenhall: Are we going back to the old brutish Brewbarry, or do we need to… Channel the new, refined Brewbarry.
Gary Young: I can do either.
Wade Brown: He's a man of culture.
David Mendenhall: I'm like, s… finely woven… Mullen Road…
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, dude, he's, he's, he's, he's, he's still… A man of the people.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget, He wears his armor, and on top, he wears his… his…
David Mendenhall: In the bathrobe.
Wade Brown: And underneath, he wears a Hawaiian shirt.
David Mendenhall: I would think that would… it would get very dirty.
David Mendenhall: the bathroom.
Kostadis Roussos: But you see, but we already covered that in character. He believes that that adds color and character to the bathrobe.
Wade Brown: That's why you start with a red bathroom.
David Mendenhall: It's all the blood just…
Wade Brown: blends in.
David Mendenhall: brown and dirty all the time.
Kostadis Roussos: That's… but… but…
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, are you gonna tell that… are you gonna tell that to him? Like…
Gary Young: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you gonna… is Vukradin gonna tell Brewbarry that his clothes look awful?
David Mendenhall: I don't think Vukradin cares about such things.
Kostadis Roussos: Really?
David Mendenhall: No.
Wade Brown: He's not a fashionista.
David Mendenhall: There's about right and wrong and music.
Gary Young: So it has to vary on the performances.
David Mendenhall: Nope.
Gary Young: I guess, I guess for Barry, it's not, he's, he's more.
David Mendenhall: Not on stage.
Gary Young: an update.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, he's on… he's at the audience. He's either backstage or in the audience. He's not on stage.
Wade Brown: He's always in the audience, cheering, 10 out of 10.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I thought, I thought, wait, hold on. I thought we said more cowbell.
Gary Young: Oh, he's the cowbell, ringer? Okay, could be.
David Mendenhall: Yo, Kyle.
David Mendenhall: We were going to the sewers, was that the plan?
Wade Brown: We're gonna do that stakeout?
David Mendenhall: Oh yeah, we're gonna do the stakeout.
Wade Brown: Gotta watch where that extra crate's getting off to.
David Mendenhall: That's right.
David Mendenhall: Let's do it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, I sent out a Brewbarry take on what's going on.
Kostadis Roussos: Had some funny moments.
Kostadis Roussos: My favorite one is…
Kostadis Roussos: 9 crates go down that lane, 8 go inside, 1 walks away on its own. Someone stopped paying that gnome on purpose, and somebody is feeding him on purpose. And either that is the same person, or it is 2, and I find out which one tonight. I am a barbarian, not a thief. I do not work in the shadows, and I let my enemy know that I am there. And yet tonight, I go quiet, because Lim asked me to, and because Soma's already unhappy with me.
Wade Brown: Poor… poor Brewbarry.
David Mendenhall: I have a very high stealth, if we need me to…
David Mendenhall: We need someone to do something stealthily.
Wade Brown: I mean, you could tag along with a familiar Iceland now.
David Mendenhall: Well, it's… Just telling you, you've got a plus 9 with advantage, so… If it's not.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you serious?
David Mendenhall: I have an actual character.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Damn.
Wade Brown: I didn't know bards got high stealth.
David Mendenhall: If you choose it…
Wade Brown: Yeah, got your feats.
Gary Young: I do have a.
David Mendenhall: And it's just because I have boots of elvenkind.
Wade Brown: Hell yeah.
Gary Young: I do have a plus 5 stealth.
David Mendenhall: Well, it's not plus 9, though.
David Mendenhall: I don't have your perception and all the other crazy things you have.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you mean you're not a… you… so what you're saying is… You can walk past
Kostadis Roussos: Valphine, without her noticing.
David Mendenhall: I don't think anybody can.
Wade Brown: I don't think anyone can do that.
Gary Young: Well, technically, my perception is only plus 7.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so yours is plus 9, so…
David Mendenhall: That's a role, right? Passive. Passive self versus passive perception, is that a thing?
Gary Young: I think you roll against my passive.
David Mendenhall: Yes, I know, I know.
David Mendenhall: That was a joke.
Kostadis Roussos: He's a jerk. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Soap.
Kostadis Roussos: Where were we? So when we last left our Noble Adventures.
Kostadis Roussos: You were playing at the Common Chord.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, right.
David Mendenhall: And we negotiated.
David Mendenhall: What a good deal.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so Petra said it was given… you negotiated 500 gold pieces as a one-time payment for all the likenesses
Kostadis Roussos: For your likeness.
David Mendenhall: Past and future.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
David Mendenhall: 500 gold, performance in 2 days. Yes, it's on the Quest Tracker.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right. So, so, so that… you're also waiting for it to be 3 AM before you head out?
Kostadis Roussos: to,
Wade Brown: Broad.
David Mendenhall: Food deliveries.
Wade Brown: Board Laid Bare. That's great.
David Mendenhall: Nice.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yep.
David Mendenhall: On the quest tracker.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. And so… and there's still the small matter of meeting Lord Neverember, but you kind of… he's…
Kostadis Roussos: He can wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Aldus hasn't contacted you about when exactly dinner is going.
David Mendenhall: Is it Neverember or Neverwinter? I'm kidding.
Kostadis Roussos: Neverember. Neverember.
David Mendenhall: Neverember.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: It is never, like, a fire ember.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I think it is. Let me just go to that. Now I got it wrong.
Wade Brown: He's never flaming. He keeps it on the DL.
David Mendenhall: It's Lord…
Kostadis Roussos: Never, Ember.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that's… I… I think Wade has it exactly right.
Kostadis Roussos: What was it?
Wade Brown: He's never flaming, he keeps it on the DL.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, never flaming.
David Mendenhall: The double entendres in these modules… Ridiculous.
David Mendenhall: Okay, and Lord Neverember… Lord Neverflaming has a new drow advisor.
Wade Brown: Great, isn't that Valphine?
David Mendenhall: No.
Wade Brown: Ow.
Wade Brown: Oh, right.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a rum It's a room.
David Mendenhall: rumor, and I suspect… Valphine will know this advisor at dinner, but we will see.
Gary Young: I'm sorry, I lost track. What… What do I?
David Mendenhall: Lord NeverEmber. Lord Never Flaming.
David Mendenhall: new drow advisor that we will.
Gary Young: Oh, right, right, right. Which we assume to be one of my siblings, in fact.
David Mendenhall: That's my… that is my guess, too, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope, okay.
Wade Brown: Everyone's related to everyone.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, I'm Greek, so this is kind of…
Wade Brown: expected.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Have we secured the capital for Brewbarry's bathroom business, or is that still in progress?
Wade Brown: I believe it's in progress.
Kostadis Roussos: What is in progress?
Wade Brown: Securing money for the.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, you've secured the money. You've secured the money.
David Mendenhall: We have. Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes,
David Mendenhall: But, oh, but the cost of import is very high.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: Right, because their shipping lanes are still…
Wade Brown: Shipping portals, whatever, are still hosed.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and House Margaster's in charge.
Wade Brown: Of course they are.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know, they deliver things on time and on schedule.
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's head out to Lim's Food Deliveries and get there by 3 AM.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: And then we can cast whatever spells we need in order to be ready.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, session prompt.
David Mendenhall: Neverwinter… we're… and the town is named Neverwinter, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: Lord, Neverember of Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: Never ever owned.
David Mendenhall: Ember… well, Ember and winter are, like, opposites, so there's that, too.
Wade Brown: That makes him a terrible, lord.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Gary Young: Well, at least he's under Margaster.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm kind of, like, curious, like, is what… what is, what's her name's take on House Margaster? I mean, is she impressed with her control and, you know, what she's doing, or is she unimpressed?
Gary Young: I think Valphine is,
Gary Young: looking at Margaster as the competition.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, that I understand.
Kostadis Roussos: I think there's gonna have to be… I think there's gonna have to be a moment where Lathander and Valphine may have to have a coming to Lathander.
David Mendenhall: Well, defender's dead, dude. Haven't you heard?
Wade Brown: Understood.
David Mendenhall: death every night.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, I need to get something to drink.
Gary Young: Okay.
Wade Brown: We drove them to alcohol.
Gary Young: And have the,
David Mendenhall: And they say.
Gary Young: They can'.
David Mendenhall: kill gods.
Gary Young: I think I have the summary photo now.
Gary Young: I'll put it in the story so far.
David Mendenhall: Wandering Tortle Tavern Menu.
Wade Brown: Tortle soup.
Wade Brown: Turtle for me, turtle soup.
Gary Young: But…
David Mendenhall: It's Turtles! Soylent green turtles!
Gary Young: It's not… it's turtle soup, not made of turtles, it's made of people.
Wade Brown: I'm okay with that.
Wade Brown: Crack nest menu?
David Mendenhall: The menu's a little pricey, that doesn't seem very realistic.
Gary Young: We can digest it, but…
David Mendenhall: 50 gold. I think it's more like, you know, 5 silvers, or something like that, or 1 silver.
Wade Brown: I didn't know they had labeled exit signs in, Neverwinter.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that's… wow.
Wade Brown: Like…
Wade Brown: Oh, shit.
David Mendenhall: compliance.
Wade Brown: Is there a ramp for, you know, to say…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, is there an ADA in, Faerun?
Kostadis Roussos: Alright,
Gary Young: Sadus, do we need to catch you up?
Kostadis Roussos: About what?
Gary Young: Deep picture.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry.
David Mendenhall: and turtle soup.
David Mendenhall: It's made with real humans.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, good lord, I'm terrified.
Wade Brown: Oh, it's from Gary, not from me.
Kostadis Roussos: I can't laughed too loud.
Gary Young: It's turtle-free.
Gary Young: But it's creative people.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Okay.
Gary Young: Fair.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, so you're at the dive, right, that used to throw you out, unpaid. It's the hardest ticket in Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Kostadis Roussos: And that, you know, one of the locals is, like, talking that the court is unaffordable now, and it's all due to Vukradin, and he sort of sees it, but, you know, kind of, like, talking about you without realizing you're standing within earshot of him.
David Mendenhall: I could tell him I'm planning on opening my own independent music studio, and if he'd like to contribute to the charitable fund.
David Mendenhall: That will speed the…
David Mendenhall: opening of a… of a pre… a low-cost, non-profit way to hear, Lathander's death on a regular basis.
Kostadis Roussos: You make that offer, okay.
David Mendenhall: And spread the word.
David Mendenhall: Awesome, we have, you know, there's a GoFundMe, and, you know.
David Mendenhall: Yeah. QR code, Venmo account, etc.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, sending stone, in this case.
David Mendenhall: All the, all the, all the Faerun equivalents.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: I take Google Pay, Apple Pay, Portal Pay.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yep. 9.27 p.m.
Gary Young: Yeah, turtle pay is good.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: So one of the things, one of the things you do learn is that as you're listening, overhearing at the local bar.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that the tide… That goes through the sewers.
Kostadis Roussos: Turns twice a day.
Kostadis Roussos: So you have to, if you're.
David Mendenhall: Hide in the sewers?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the, the, the, from the river.
David Mendenhall: There's a tide in the sewers? A river has a tide?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know, the town is right next to the sea.
Kostadis Roussos: The tides come in, and so there's, like.
David Mendenhall: How many moons does this planet have?
Kostadis Roussos: Fine? You asked?
Gary Young: That's an easy question to answer.
David Mendenhall: Just the one.
Wade Brown: It just rotates It revolves really fast.
Gary Young: It has one moon named Saloon.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it actually has one.
David Mendenhall: I'll say Loon, of course, same. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: It's got saloon, and it's got the tiers of Saloon.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: That's true.
David Mendenhall: So, there should be a tidal effect from both moons.
Kostadis Roussos: No, because the other ones are actually asteroids. Cluster of meters and asteroids.
David Mendenhall: They're not sufficiently gravitational.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: You're telling me?
Kostadis Roussos: S.
David Mendenhall: Not really moon.
Wade Brown: Yeah, they're… they're just comets.
David Mendenhall: They're asteroids. So the one moon, then.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, well, according to it, just so you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Experiences two high tides and two low tides each day.
David Mendenhall: There you go, see? Not 1 and 1, there you go. Too high and too low, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Wade Brown: Jesus.
Wade Brown: That's murder on trade.
Kostadis Roussos: That… okay.
Gary Young: I should take effect underground, too, right?
David Mendenhall: So it's a 6-hour cycle.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: And 2 daily high tides and 2 low tides.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, so it's a 6-hour cycle.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So, yes, sorry, I should've.
David Mendenhall: High to low is 3 hours.
Kostadis Roussos: So, yes, so there's this period of time when it's low tide.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, no, high to low. High to low is 6 hours, 6…
David Mendenhall: High to low is 6 hours.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, yes.
David Mendenhall: We want to be in the sewer for… at low tide.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, which just happens to be conveniently it.
Wade Brown: 3M.
David Mendenhall: We have about 3 hours, maybe 4, before things start to get really uncomfortable.
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly.
David Mendenhall: I'm hurtful.
Wade Brown: I mean, I can hang out underwater indefinitely.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: That's fine, can you go for that?
David Mendenhall: behind.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, you know, that's kind of like, you overhear that amongst the discussion, it's not directed at you.
David Mendenhall: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so I presume you're gonna now,
Kostadis Roussos: There, I presume you're now gonna go, spy on, what's your name?
David Mendenhall: Did he want to make a charitable contribution to GoFundMe for the…
David Mendenhall: He's not interested. Did he even believe me? Does he even think that I am Vukradin? Do I need to explain it to him?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, you can roll your persuasion, right? Your persuasion isn't…
David Mendenhall: Okay, well, I mean, we know, okay, sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Agreed.
David Mendenhall: 17.
Kostadis Roussos: you know, he's on the drunk side, right? And…
Kostadis Roussos: And you're so charming and, like, so convincing that.
David Mendenhall: fees.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, man, I don't have a lot of money, but he hands you over 10 gold pieces.
David Mendenhall: Wow, that's pretty generous, actually.
Wade Brown: That's a hell of a domain.
David Mendenhall: random nobody. We need to put that in the correct… that goes in the studio fund, so that does not go in the regular coffers, but thank you very much for contributing to the studio fund, that's awesome.
Kostadis Roussos: he goes, he pauses, you know, he's a little bit on the drunk side, and goes, like, like, do I get on, like, is there some kind of, like, signage for people who contributed to it?
David Mendenhall: Absolutely. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And his…
David Mendenhall: There are different tiers of giving levels, actually. 10 gold pieces puts you at the,
Wade Brown: Premier or the Plus, which one?
David Mendenhall: At the plus level, yeah, you're not quite at Premier yet.
Kostadis Roussos: Because I… Yeah.
David Mendenhall: You're at plus level. 10 gold is a lot for a rando.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, you know, he's happy to hear that.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we need his name, we need to write his name down, because we'll have to put it in the program notes, and…
Wade Brown: It'd be the…
David Mendenhall: Per year.
Wade Brown: Good section.
David Mendenhall: A year. I mean, then, if you want to be in next year, you'll have to donate again, but for one year, that's a long time.
Gary Young: Yeah, we call this Patreon.
David Mendenhall: It's my Patreon, exactly.
Wade Brown: This is where it comes from, patronage.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, let's… I need a name.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, let's go get.
Wade Brown: Bob.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, I have all these books with all these names.
Wade Brown: Yeah, but we're gonna make fun of them, and you're gonna be mad that we're gonna make fun of them.
Kostadis Roussos: No, actually, I… no, I don't get mad.
David Mendenhall: But before we go, should I go around and, like, try to convince other people to contribute to the Studio Fund? How much time do we have?
Kostadis Roussos: You… it's like 3… it's like at 3 AM, it's like, let's… you got… you got plenty of time.
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's do… let's hit up a few more people, let's see how it goes here.
Wade Brown: If…
David Mendenhall: I'll do 5 more. 1… 2… 3… Or… And 5.
David Mendenhall: That's some pretty good rolls there.
David Mendenhall: 25, 26, 25, 17, 17.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: Never below your minimum of 15.
David Mendenhall: The minimum 17.
Wade Brown: Oh, your minimum's 17 now, it used to be 15, I thought.
David Mendenhall: It used to be 15, yeah, it's gone up.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Wade Brown: Inflation on your persuasion.
David Mendenhall: We leveled up, man.
Kostadis Roussos: One guy rolled a natural 20 and just looks at you and goes.
Kostadis Roussos: realizes you're the real Vukradin. Yeah. But says, you know, that he's already done his charitable giving for this year.
David Mendenhall: Okay, that's fine. I'm not here to pressure anybody.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, any.
David Mendenhall: The benefits are all on you, if you can be at the, you know, plus or premier level, like, I'm cool. I just like fans.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and he says, biggest fan, biggest fan.
David Mendenhall: Oh, Bigger Than Brewbarry?
Gary Young: Brewbarry's very large. In fact, he's huge in Japan sometimes.
Wade Brown: Do you have a 20-foot reach?
Kostadis Roussos: He… no, he's not that big. He looks at… he looks at Brewbarry, goes, no, I'm not that big.
David Mendenhall: Yeah. Okay.
David Mendenhall: It's alright. Nobody's as big as Brewbarry, that's just how it.
Kostadis Roussos: You know. So, yeah, so the third guy's just like, you know,
Kostadis Roussos: And the fourth person also,
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Kostadis Roussos: So, 4 of the people all are, you know, enthralled by your, you know, your Buy your thing.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So… Alright, so one of them is…
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so there's, like, these… one person's name, Wick, Sabbatha, Old Hesp, And Ondrelle Kass.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
David Mendenhall: That's great. Well, let's add them to the program notes, and
Kostadis Roussos: Here, I'll just put the names here so that you have.
David Mendenhall: That's awesome.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: by the way, like, the second guy, Wick, you know, is really excited, has no idea who Lathander's death is, you know, and is really into the patron of the Arts and doesn't really believe you are,
Kostadis Roussos: Vukradin, but doesn't really care if you are or not Vukradin. He just thinks it's awesome that you're putting together a music school.
Wade Brown: School?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that's what you said, studio, right?
David Mendenhall: school, studio, they're all the same, right? If you have a studio, it's for training people, that's just how it goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he kind of assumes that.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Sabbatha is, like…
Kostadis Roussos: is also very, you know… and she's, like, staring at Brewbarry and giving him the, you know, look over, and can't help but comment about how he's committed to the Brewbarry look.
David Mendenhall: Yes, he is quite bulging, isn't he?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: Rippling.
David Mendenhall: Exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: The last guy you meet is Old Hesp.
Kostadis Roussos: And you recognize him.
Kostadis Roussos: Or rather, he recognizes you.
Kostadis Roussos: And says, I remember when you used to play to an empty room.
David Mendenhall: Yeah?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Did you come? Did you come? Did I give you your money back at the end of.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he… yes, you did. He said that if I didn't love it, you wouldn't take my… if I didn't give you a 10 out of 10, I wouldn't give.
David Mendenhall: I know, that's how honest I am. Well, what do you think now?
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses, he goes, now this is a friggin' expensive place to be, everybody's gotta look cool.
David Mendenhall: Well, come to the new studio, when it's up and running.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, it doesn't have the look, that feel, that, that gritty…
David Mendenhall: We're gonna get it back. We're gonna get it back.
Kostadis Roussos: This is too commer… this is too commercial.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, yeah, I agree.
Kostadis Roussos: It's too commercial. Too… I mean, Petra's turned this into a money-making operation. I gotta respect her, she's, you know, she turned… I mean, I remember when that table points where, you know, the Brewbarry table.
Kostadis Roussos: Was, you know, that was not leather and shiny and with a plaque.
Kostadis Roussos: And then he goes, and we didn't have this kind of fancy food here.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: A little bit more money.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you raised, 10 little pieces to a.
David Mendenhall: Another time, I'll take it. Sounds good.
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's go, do some… spelunking.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you're at the third hour.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
David Mendenhall: you casting…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so tell me about your cast.
David Mendenhall: trade.
Wade Brown: I find familiar.
Wade Brown: Dropped it up in the chat a little bit ago, but…
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we just have to stay within 100 feet. I'm going to, create a little rat. I see and hear everything the rat hears.
David Mendenhall: 100 feet is… Pretty close.
Wade Brown: Yeah, but, you know, we… we can be, like, on the other side of walls. It's not, like, line of sight 100 feet.
David Mendenhall: Hmm, okay…
Wade Brown: There's… there's corners and everywhere, you know, we… we can be… we can make it work.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Okay. So, you're at a grill, that goes into the, I guess, sewers.
Wade Brown: Oh, okay. Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Yup.
Kostadis Roussos: So it's kind of like aqueduct steps, and kind of, like, thing. There's whetstone. There's, two crate carriers.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you can see them, dropping down the crates.
Wade Brown: All 9 of them?
Kostadis Roussos: Nope, yeah, all 9 of them.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: So we… so we want one person to track down the gnome, right, crate 9.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: We want other… also, we want to track the people who dropped them, so we want to do two things.
Kostadis Roussos: You want to track that, or the gnome, like…
David Mendenhall: We could…
Wade Brown: What, you said you got your high stealth.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: If you want, I can track the gnome. You guys can go do the… the sewers.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown: Well, I'm tracking the crate.
David Mendenhall: Which crate?
Wade Brown: The ninth crate, the one that.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Wade Brown: go on a limb, because I'm more concerned about my friend's shady business.
Gary Young: That's why I look great.
David Mendenhall: We're not gonna follow… Okay, so you want me to follow them back into the sewers?
David Mendenhall: That seems pretty dangerous. One person in the… one party member in the sewers.
Wade Brown: I see. Alright, we can send the rat that way, then. You can follow the crate.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so… so what hap… what's happening is Valphine, Soma, Brewbarry are…
David Mendenhall: Tracking the familiar 100 feet behind.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, as it follows the two… the two delivery men back to the sewers, they brought in the same Dahan.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, hold on. Okay.
Wade Brown: We say above ground.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, j-just… Just to be clear.
Kostadis Roussos: So, what happens is that they just drop these two… these, these boxes near this grill.
Kostadis Roussos: Right? And… They just walk away.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, they're just walking away. So, what is it that you want to… what… what… so what… so you see a bunch of crates.
Kostadis Roussos: being deposited. What you know… what you look at the… what you notice about the crates is they clearly don't have
Kostadis Roussos: the Commission Harbor mark on them.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, meaning that they've been smuggled in here somehow?
Wade Brown: Yeah, no, we knew that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I'm just, just reminding you.
Kostadis Roussos: And…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, as they're packing them away, one of the carriers stops halfway, as is, like, leading these crates, looks down into the dark, and then walks away.
Wade Brown: Like, down at the grates, or the…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, at the grove where the crates are from, where the crates are.
David Mendenhall: Who is your name?
David Mendenhall: Is your rat chasing the… to people?
Wade Brown: The route's gonna go whichever way leads to the sewer.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So who's… so is somebody following these guys… the carriers, or…
Wade Brown: I think since the crate was gonna go underground, we were gonna send Dave after the… or the Vukradin over…
Wade Brown: Topside with the people, right?
David Mendenhall: So, look, the… The crates got dropped off. Lim's gonna come out and take 8 of the crates.
Wade Brown: Right.
David Mendenhall: And she's not gonna take a 9th crate.
David Mendenhall: Bukan is gonna stick around, and stealthily wait to see who comes to get to the 9th crate, and…
David Mendenhall: will… track that.
Wade Brown: Oh, these… so these are the guys… these guys are going down into the sewer? I thought they were just walking out.
David Mendenhall: They're coming from the sewers, yes.
Wade Brown: Right, right, they came up from the delivery.
David Mendenhall: So if you want to go to the sewers, you're gonna have to follow them.
Wade Brown: Yes, yes, the rational.
Kostadis Roussos: They're not actually going back into the sewers.
Kostadis Roussos: They're walking away.
David Mendenhall: Well, I think you should still talk.
Wade Brown: I'm gonna follow them, yeah.
Gary Young: So everyone other than Crawdin is gonna…
Gary Young: trail these guys, and then Vukradin's gonna trail the crate.
Gary Young: Is that right?
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Gary Young: Okay, I can, I can…
Wade Brown: Sorry, I'll get there, I'm a little slow.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So,
Wade Brown: They come out of the sewers, they drop the crates, and then they just walk on through town, which way?
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Yeah, they just kind of… they don't… they don't kind of look at each other.
Kostadis Roussos: So they kind of, like, Act as if they don't know each other, and they sort of… split up.
Wade Brown: That nonchalant whistling.
David Mendenhall: So if they split up, that's gonna make them hard to follow. You're gonna have to choose one or split again.
Gary Young: I want to roll an insight check to figure out which of them looks like the one in charge.
Gary Young: relative to each other. Now, who's the more senior member?
Wade Brown: -Oh.
Gary Young: 12.
David Mendenhall: You did not roll a 1.
Gary Young: Hold on.
Gary Young: And then… particle depression.
Gary Young: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Gary Young: So that is a 19.
David Mendenhall: Art inspiration. Okay, you used the last one.
David Mendenhall: No more bardic inspiration until we long rest.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: That was Williams. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so there were two guys. One of them was… One of them,
Kostadis Roussos: One of them, as I said.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, so you had to put the 9th… put the eight crates, and what… the 9th crate was put on the ledge.
Kostadis Roussos: And the guy who put it on the ledge looked down as if he was looking for something and walked away.
Kostadis Roussos: So, with your… the other guy just was stacking the boxes.
Wade Brown: I'd follow the guy with the… who paid attention to the ledge.
Wade Brown: He knows something. He knows something's coming out of that thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so… Are you gonna… They… so as they… so they split out, and they go into different… directions.
Kostadis Roussos: Which one? So you follow, I'm presumably?
Wade Brown: The one who looked down at the sewers, you know, who seemed more than just grunt work labor.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Who's the… who's next to the crate? Just, I want to make sure I know that.
David Mendenhall: Vukradin.
Gary Young: a crop.
Wade Brown: crowded.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so I'll stop here for… and the rest of you are following the carrier?
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: I could handle this myself, guys, you don't trust me?
Kostadis Roussos: Some… so, something comes up for it, and it is not a person. Small, quick, brass and leather, cat-sized, moving with the unhurried competence of a thing following instructions. It takes the crate and goes back down.
David Mendenhall: Okay, Vukradin will pursue stealthily.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown: This is my concern. Vukradin ends up going into the sewers now, and…
David Mendenhall: I'll be fine.
Wade Brown: One person in the sewers? Alright.
David Mendenhall: got advantage.
Kostadis Roussos: Never.
Wade Brown: Tell me the odds.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, this is the end of Vukradin, alright.
David Mendenhall: Only a 1 in 400 chance of disaster. It'll be fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Denvar… the guy you're following goes for… stops at a cook shot that's open at the fourth hour.
Wade Brown: Can't be a lot of those.
Kostadis Roussos: So there's not a lot of those.
Kostadis Roussos: And he seems to be happily eating it.
David Mendenhall: By the way, Wade, you have one of the sending stones, and I have the other sending stone.
Wade Brown: Good to know.
Wade Brown: So we could have little walkie-talkies over. Yeah.
David Mendenhall: We have walkie-talkies.
Wade Brown: He's not eating turtle soup or anything at this hour, is he?
Wade Brown: It's not the Board Laid Bare he's at, of course, he's somewhere else.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, are you… so, by the way, the clock is ticking, so about 15 minutes have elapsed.
Wade Brown: Okay, I… I mean, he's…
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just saying… I'm just telling you because there's the tide. That's my point.
Wade Brown: Oh, right, right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: So… So do you want to jump him? Do… he's like… He's like…
Kostadis Roussos: eating his food. Do you want to walk up to him? Like, what do you want to do with him?
Wade Brown: He's just eating alone, he's not talking to anybody, not, not,
Kostadis Roussos: It's late at night, it's 4 AM, you know, the locals there are, you know.
David Mendenhall: Remember, we promised Lim we're not gonna spook her connections.
David Mendenhall: Or you promised them.
Wade Brown: Thank you so much.
Wade Brown: I mean, I'm not trying to get her, you know, out of business. I don't know, I kind of want to see where he goes next. I mean, just stopping off for a snack, that's… that's… doesn't tell us anything, and spooking him doesn't seem like, you know, kosher.
Kostadis Roussos: You could walk up to him and talk to him. I mean, he… looking at him, Valphine's intuition tells you that he's just what he appears to be.
Gary Young: A delivery guy.
Kostadis Roussos: A delivery guy.
Wade Brown: Guy with no knowledge. Yeah.
Gary Young: Well, we want to know, like, who hired him, though. Like, what is their route for smuggling, I think?
Wade Brown: I mean, I think we've missed the route at this point. I think he's just…
Wade Brown: Going about his daily business.
Gary Young: Well, he picks up stuff every day, right?
Wade Brown: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Like, if you find out where he lives and where he goes, like, maybe you wanna…
Wade Brown: Yeah, I agree.
David Mendenhall: night, you want to see where he is at 2AM, but in order to do that, you need to figure out, like, where he's going to be at 2AM, that sort of thing.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Okay, take multiple nights to stake him out. Awesome.
David Mendenhall: play.
Wade Brown: Brewbarry will be happy about that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, we'll stop here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, make a wisdom saving throw.
Wade Brown: Me?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I'm talking to Dave.
Wade Brown: Oh, okay.
David Mendenhall: Wisdom, save.
David Mendenhall: Okay… I don't think that's gonna go very well.
Wade Brown: Okay, you've got advantage.
David Mendenhall: Not on Saves.
Wade Brown: Oh…
Kostadis Roussos: what happens?
David Mendenhall: Natural one.
Gary Young: Good times.
Wade Brown: Oh, no.
David Mendenhall: I mean, okay, there's some passive charm effect or something.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so what happens is you suddenly become disinterested with where you're going.
Kostadis Roussos: Decide that this is utterly boring.
Kostadis Roussos: And totally not worth your time, and start walking away.
Wade Brown: turn into Brewbarry.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, you'll get overwhelmed with this confused, like, Like, like, confused… confusion. Alright.
David Mendenhall: A passive confusion effect. Alright, awesome.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it wasn't a passing confusion effect.
David Mendenhall: Well, it can't have been cast directly on me.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
David Mendenhall: This is, like, an area effect.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, it was an area effect.
David Mendenhall: And where do I wander off to?
Kostadis Roussos: comment.
David Mendenhall: word.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, not to the Common Chord. As you walk away, I just… I just need to read one more thing, because I took up… made a lot of notes here.
Kostadis Roussos: A minute,
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: What is he?
Kostadis Roussos: You, you,
Kostadis Roussos: So, you see a collection, you see a guy standing in front of you with a bunch of
Kostadis Roussos: Other kind of,
Kostadis Roussos: He's looking, he looks at you kind of like… He looks at you funny.
Kostadis Roussos: Says, how the hell did you get over here?
David Mendenhall: I don't know.
David Mendenhall: Where am I?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… He looks at you and he says.
Kostadis Roussos: Why… so, you were disinterested in following the tunnel, but you still remember where you were. You basically decided that this was not the right way to go. Do you see what I'm saying? It's not that you got confused, it's like the whole idea of going down this path seemed, like, not interesting anymore.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: So he asked me why I'm here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: And then I say, Because I'm not over there.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you funny and goes, Role and insight check.
David Mendenhall: Oh yeah, because that's one of my roles. Why do you have me doing all the roles I'm not good at?
Kostadis Roussos: But…
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Because you're not trying to convince.
David Mendenhall: Love it.
Kostadis Roussos: Here's… well, hold on. You're supposed to roll your persuasion to start talking to him, like, he's…
Kostadis Roussos: pressing you, and you're just sitting there, so I'm just like… I was assuming you'd start rolling your persuasion and try to convince them.
David Mendenhall: Why do I need to convince them of anything?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm gonna find out what he wants, or why he's here.
David Mendenhall: Well, that's not persuasion.
David Mendenhall: Alright, well, I rolled a 7, so go ahead.
Kostadis Roussos: You, you, you, you notice nothing about him.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I would say so.
Wade Brown: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Alright, so I… I guess I want to talk my way out of the situation, so that I can reunite with my friends, because that's more interesting than the stakeout I was supposed to be doing.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh?
David Mendenhall: Is that what you're saying? Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
David Mendenhall: Sure, I can talk myself out of this.
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's… he's not… that's the thing, that what you're… the impression you get is he doesn't… he's not, like, angry at you.
Kostadis Roussos: He's, like, confused as to what are you doing here?
David Mendenhall: But I don't know what I'm doing here.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you do know that you were looking after the…
Wade Brown: Right, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: You do know that, but why you're specifically there, you don't.
David Mendenhall: Oh, well, I wouldn't want to reveal that, so that's deception.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so I just want to say, you…
David Mendenhall: Alright, fine, I'll do a deception roll. 23.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, and you've successfully convinced him you don't know Where you are.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, there you go. I'm lost.
David Mendenhall: I don't know what… I don't know how I got here, I just…
Wade Brown: Where's my mom?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, long turn.
David Mendenhall: Should have taken that left at Albuquerque.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, Slicks his, Licks his finger.
Kostadis Roussos: And says, well, that's, And so… He, he says, well, This is my territory.
David Mendenhall: This is your territory.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, this is my territory. Wow.
Wade Brown: Supers.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Did you want me to go?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I'd want to know why you're in my territory.
David Mendenhall: Oh, I'm sorry that I got lost. I'm happy to leave. Could you point me in the direction of Lim's?
David Mendenhall: Cafe, that's… that's where I want to be headed.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you funny. Lim's Cafe?
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Huh.
David Mendenhall: We're friends.
Kostadis Roussos: That's interesting. Why are you… and he suddenly becomes very interested in the fact that you're friends with Lim.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He's, like, looking at you very, kind of, like, suspiciously now.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: He's toying with the idea of, like, whether he should do something with you.
Kostadis Roussos: But then…
Kostadis Roussos: He recognizes you somehow, he goes, Are you that singer?
David Mendenhall: Exactly. And Lim's a fan.
Kostadis Roussos: What are you doing down here, man?
David Mendenhall: I told you, I got lost!
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you and says, Vukradin… you're Vukradin, right?
Kostadis Roussos: And, one of the guys standing next to him is really smiling and very happy. He goes.
Kostadis Roussos: This is… is this really Vukradin?
David Mendenhall: Do you guys want autographs?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, they're, they're like, we'd love some autographs.
David Mendenhall: Sure, we can do some autographs, but then I gotta be going.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, sure… Maybe you can…
David Mendenhall: Point me in the right direction.
Kostadis Roussos: You know what, we're gonna do one better, we're gonna take you there.
David Mendenhall: Alright, sounds good.
Kostadis Roussos: We don't want you to get lost again, Mr. Vukradin.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
David Mendenhall: Lim will be thrilled.
Kostadis Roussos: And then he pauses, you have the notes. It's very dangerous down here.
David Mendenhall: Is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's, it's, it's,
David Mendenhall: Idris in your territory?
Kostadis Roussos: Well… he goes…
David Mendenhall: I would think you would keep a very… you seem like a very, you know, safe kind of individual. I'm sure you.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes.
David Mendenhall: place ShipShape.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Mr. Vukradin and I agree with you.
Kostadis Roussos: Fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: But I have to tell you that the reason I was out here, and I was a little bit concerned when I saw you, and I have to say, I'm very glad that I was able to recognize you from… you know, I… one of my guys over here tells me that you have a deal with a friend of mine.
David Mendenhall: At the Common Chord?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, at the Toe mine.
David Mendenhall: Mountain's Toe Mine. Oh, yeah…
Kostadis Roussos: Zeleen…
Gary Young: This is a merger at grade.
David Mendenhall: Oh, I didn't know you knew him.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, he… well, you know, knows that.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we spent some time in Phandalin, yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he said that he had a business relationship with you, I said that he was full of shit.
David Mendenhall: No, no, that's true, that's true. Yeah, they haven't produced very much yet, but they say they're working hard.
Kostadis Roussos: He… he kind of just… he laughs.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: That's how I feel about it, too.
Kostadis Roussos: He… he laughs.
Kostadis Roussos: He laughs, and he says, look, look, here's, here's a… I manage the tunnels here.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, and make sure that…
David Mendenhall: Oh, you're the tunnel manager.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, a tunnel manager.
David Mendenhall: So this is your territory, and you have all the tunnels.
Kostadis Roussos: Not all the tunnels, but the tunnels in this area.
David Mendenhall: The tunnels in this area, interesting, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. There's… all I know is that…
Kostadis Roussos: And so I'm a little bit, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: Two months ago, things started to come up the floodline.
David Mendenhall: Hudlime.
Kostadis Roussos: And basically, as Ed, he goes… he explains a tunnel that would… that was… that would flood every…
David Mendenhall: I don't know anything about tunnels, man, I'm a musician.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, I don't know, man, it's like, I've been having this problem with these tunnels, I've lost men, so we just don't go there anymore.
David Mendenhall: Did you need some help with that? Because we're looking… we're trying to look for, like, ways to make money. Like, we have some abilities, me and my friends. Like, if you need some help, maybe we can help you.
Kostadis Roussos: it goes… And then he starts talking about, well…
David Mendenhall: 25.
Kostadis Roussos: He, he, he, he, he didn't, he didn't even have to roll through it.
Kostadis Roussos: You want me?
David Mendenhall: at home.
David Mendenhall: He really wants my help, he really wants my help.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, because there's, There's a…
Kostadis Roussos: Well, here's the thing, is one of the guys who escaped there said there was some…
Kostadis Roussos: There was some kind of creature that they'd never seen before.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: It looked like…
David Mendenhall: Creature stuff.
Kostadis Roussos: It looked like a spider, but it had all the wrong colors.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: You guys, you would have remembered this from the mine. The webs were… the webs it created were all wrong. They were not… there was something really off about them. Anyway.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: We decided…
David Mendenhall: experience with that.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, well, that's, that's, you know what, I mean, and, and he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. Vukradin, I know this is too much to ask, but could you get me some tickets to the Common Chord?
David Mendenhall: I can ask, you know, I…
David Mendenhall: we have kind of an arm's length relationship with the Common Chord, but I will ask for you.
Kostadis Roussos: That's all I could ask for.
David Mendenhall: Alright, let's do some autographs, and then we gotta be on our way.
Wade Brown: Cheers.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright,
Kostadis Roussos: All right. So, you, you appear. Alright, meanwhile, the rest of you, this guy, you know, after he has his, dinner and his lunch.
Wade Brown: And dinner at 4 a.m.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no. It was breakfast,
Kostadis Roussos: Heads to what you assume is his place of rest, and goes to sleep.
David Mendenhall: So now you know where he lives.
Wade Brown: It's just a night shift, so what part of town does he live in?
Kostadis Roussos: He lives in… I was not anticipating this part of the branch, but that's okay.
Wade Brown: How far from the, the… yeah.
David Mendenhall: I'll be right back.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to pull up the map.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll put him in the Bluelake District.
Wade Brown: Blue Lake, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll just put a note here.
Wade Brown: I mean, we sent the rat in.
Wade Brown: Just see if I can find any, you know.
Wade Brown: Any odd signs, any, any receipts, any, any sort of pay stubs, anything to get a, a sense.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, this guy is just, like, he's… he is what he is. He's just… he's just a guy who…
Kostadis Roussos: collects thing. The one thing you will say, though, is that for
Kostadis Roussos: As you're starting to look around, he's making a little bit more money than you just make For,
Wade Brown: I mean, that's something to say, right? Has he got nice clothes? Does he have, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I'm saying, like, you know, you're piecing it together, like.
Kostadis Roussos: somebody who just carries good doesn't go spend money at a restaurant at 4am.
Wade Brown: Yeah, he's a little overcompensated for his job.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: This is…
Wade Brown: No signs, no,
Kostadis Roussos: No, but…
Wade Brown: No marks, no insignias, nothing, nothing for the rat to spot?
Kostadis Roussos: No, nothing… no, there's no… there's no… there's no insignia, it's just he's a guy who apparently has found a good gig.
Wade Brown: Oh shit, I want that gig.
Gary Young: So, is it… does it look.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, if you want to run drugs, that is available as a career weighed, but I don't recommend it.
Wade Brown: Aww.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it worked well for the Dread Pirate Roberts!
Gary Young: So, is he in a house, or is he in an apartment?
Kostadis Roussos: is in a… place with many rooms, how about I put it that way?
David Mendenhall: A hotel.
Gary Young: Okay, so he has a landlord.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he has a landlord.
Gary Young: Who we could potentially ask questions about him of.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, absolutely.
Gary Young: But it's middle of the night, huh?
Kostadis Roussos: You can wait till the morning, like 7am.
David Mendenhall: morning. Yeah, it sounds like, like, an SRO type.
David Mendenhall: Place.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I imagine what an SRO is.
David Mendenhall: Single room occupancy.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that one of those, yes.
Wade Brown: High efficiency flat.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a… it's a… yeah, that's…
Kostadis Roussos: So it's one of those things, right? It's a high-efficiency flat, I mean, you know, there's a landlord, there's a lot of random people in there.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: So he's kind of like,
Kostadis Roussos: looking at you, you know, he's… he's in his bedroom, there's a… there's a person sitting there, obviously looks like the person who runs the place,
Kostadis Roussos: Have you guys just walk up to them, or…
Wade Brown: Yeah, no, I mean, we're… we can't spook them indirectly, so, just talk.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: landlord. Alright. Okay, we just had some questions. We wanted to know,
Wade Brown: What's it cost to live here? I think is the first one we need to know.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, she goes, I don't see many turtles around here.
Wade Brown: That's…
Gary Young: Voila.
Wade Brown: what I asked.
David Mendenhall: It's, it's a racist SRO.
Wade Brown: Yeah, jeez.
David Mendenhall: humans only.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, she's…
David Mendenhall: Goodly, goodly races only.
Kostadis Roussos: No, she's not racist. She's like, I thought turtles carried their house on their shoulders, so they didn't need a place to stay.
David Mendenhall: Oh, wow. No, not real.
Wade Brown: I see what you think of us. I can't live in this thing. It merely protects me.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh!
Wade Brown: I actually have a nice cabin out in the woods, out by, oh god, where did we start? In the winter.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Well, outside of it. I was not in Neverwinter proper.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So, she kind of looked… the guy looks at you and goes, oh, well, I learned a new thing. I did not know that turtles did not live in their shells.
Kostadis Roussos: I guess you're not like… I guess you're not like turtles.
Wade Brown: No, no, we have… Very… that's kind of slanderous to us.
Kostadis Roussos: He suddenly realizes that he's… he suddenly finally figures out… he sort of notices Valphine and Brewbarry, and suddenly realizes that maybe this was not the right person to make his commentary. He goes, I'm just asking a question.
Wade Brown: Oh, oh, I'm just asking questions, I see.
Wade Brown: I'm just touching questions guy has entered the chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Just asking questions.
Wade Brown: Look.
Wade Brown: I'll pretend I didn't hear some of that. I just… I want to know what it costs to live here, and, you know, what kind of people normally stay in a place like this.
Wade Brown: You could say I'm looking for a place for my, you know, my shell sprouts in the future.
Kostadis Roussos: he goes, well, look, you know, I mean, first of all, you know, we'll take… we don't care. We're an equal opportunity housing establishment.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, don't…
Wade Brown: It's so progressive.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, it's not about progressive, it's like, money's money, man, I don't care who's got it.
Kostadis Roussos: I ask every question. He looks at Valphine and goes, you're a drow.
Gary Young: Very astute.
Kostadis Roussos: I thought Drow didn't like the sunlight.
Gary Young: Oh, I love the sunlight.
Wade Brown: Did this guy just come out of the.
David Mendenhall: Every conversation was about race, but he's not racist.
Wade Brown: Oh, he's you as a surprise, dude.
Gary Young: I love to spend life.
Kostadis Roussos: He's asking questions.
Wade Brown: It's, it's not… it's not our duty to educate him.
Gary Young: pain.
Wade Brown: He needs to learn on his own. He needs to put in the work.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll stop here.
Wade Brown: No, it's…
David Mendenhall: I'm glad I'm not there to witness it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes,
Wade Brown: We're laying it all to you on the Sending Stones, don't worry.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that's right.
Wade Brown: Get a load of this guy!
Wade Brown: So, yeah, you're just… you just take money, you don't ask questions, so you don't know anything about your tenants, you don't know about that,
Wade Brown: Oh, how do we…
Gary Young: How do you deal with the KYC laws in here?
Wade Brown: No problem.
Kostadis Roussos: Hmm… He goes, look, this is one of these,
Kostadis Roussos: this is what… this is a, you know, this is a kind of place where you better have some cash up front to stay, you know? So it turns out it's kind of, like, not the kind of place where someone who's a day laborer would live.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it seems odd. You never, you never do any sort of background check, you never, you know, make sure that people have the gold that they, you know, claim they're gonna have after months, you know?
Kostadis Roussos: No, he… he's like, I… he goes, I don't… I'm not… I don't… I don't scry on my customers.
Wade Brown: I don't believe that. Given the racism you presume, I'm sure you scry on certain ones of them, don't you?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he noticed Brewbarry's, pecs.
Wade Brown: Jiggling about.
Kostadis Roussos: At this point, he's going like, look, look, I don't want any trouble.
Kostadis Roussos: If you want a place to stay here, I'll give you a discount.
Wade Brown: Really, we just want to know about one of your tenants.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: We asked him about the, you know, the gentleman we, you know, followed back here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, goes… You mean Denvar?
Wade Brown: Denvar. Yeah. That's more than we came with, we got a name.
David Mendenhall: Name!
Wade Brown: Denvar!
David Mendenhall: Denvar, it's going on the quest tracker.
Wade Brown: Denvar, Colorado.
David Mendenhall: R.
Kostadis Roussos: Cause, yeah.
David Mendenhall: will soon.
Wade Brown: Yes, yes, we mean Denvar.
David Mendenhall: Denvar…
Wade Brown: We, he dropped something, you know, last night.
Wade Brown: We saw him skulking about in the, the alleyway super late at night, and he dropped a little pouch. We'd like to return it to him.
Gary Young: Making a delivery.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, hold on, hold on, there was one… there was one detail I forgot to tell you.
Wade Brown: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Every… he's got… He, he's got,
Wade Brown: the whole world.
Kostadis Roussos: He's got, chits, like, you know, say, like, his, his, the job, right?
Wade Brown: Yeah, see, this is what the rat was going in looking for.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I forgot, I forgot, I forgot, like, I had to put my notes together, right? So,
Kostadis Roussos: You know, so this is, you know, he has his chits to tell him that if he does the job, this would be the… and he's got 7-10 days of them in order.
Kostadis Roussos: Each one of them reads, 9 crates, 3rd hour, 8 up, 1 down.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and there's a weekly settlement.
Wade Brown: Third up, one down.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, 8 up, 1 down, so basically.
Wade Brown: Oh, ADAP, sorry, okay, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Eight up, one, ate up, went down.
Wade Brown: Yeah, but yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: one down.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a client, a housemark, and no name anywhere on any of them.
Wade Brown: And the… all his deliveries… 100% of his delivery chits are the same. They're all this one thing. He literally has one job.
Wade Brown: Yeah. It is. Wow. Yeah, no, that's not suspicious.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so it's like somebody… it's like… and there's all… they all look settled, right? They have the,
Wade Brown: The, yeah, the checks on them, whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right.
Wade Brown: And stamp of payment.
Wade Brown: But no, nothing identifiable on them other than just…
Wade Brown: They clearly seem to be related to this one contract.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Wade Brown: Denvar.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright,
Wade Brown: So, yeah, does the, the racist establishment owner, have any… any information on Denvar beyond a name?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, one thing you… one thing…
David Mendenhall: What is the landlord's name?
Kostadis Roussos: The landlord's name.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, I hadn't…
Wade Brown: Uncle Tom.
David Mendenhall: Uncle Tom. Perfect. I love it.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
David Mendenhall: Done.
Kostadis Roussos: That's just… Hey.
David Mendenhall: Eye on the nose, man.
Kostadis Roussos: It's a little bit too on the nose.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So,
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, so… so, sorry, so he… he's… So there's, like, there's… there's a whole bunch of these, and one of the things you do notice is that today.
Kostadis Roussos: Later in the day, is the one that… one of the chits has not been settled.
Kostadis Roussos: Nice.
Wade Brown: I, okay,
Kostadis Roussos: So, like, there's 7, but the seventh one has not been paid for.
Wade Brown: And so that was the one that he just, presumably delivered. Yeah, so I guess we have reason to follow him once he wakes up, don't we?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: Yeah, that's…
David Mendenhall: I'm gonna go collect payment?
David Mendenhall: Is that,
Wade Brown: I assume he… I assume he needs to, you know, be able to afford a place like this. Yeah, he needs the money pretty quick.
Wade Brown: In fact, we could ask the landlord, you know, is Denvar settled up on his bills?
David Mendenhall: Dead bar.
Wade Brown: Dead fire.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he goes, he owes me some money today.
Wade Brown: Yeah?
David Mendenhall: Oh, okay…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: If he doesn't pay up today…
Wade Brown: Yeah, so he's… he's motivated.
David Mendenhall: won't be it tomorrow.
Wade Brown: You know, he's just sleeping in his room right now, right? Like…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, well, I mean, he's got till the end of the day, and he's a good customer. He's quiet, he doesn't bother anybody.
Wade Brown: I'll bet.
Gary Young: Good guy, huh?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, totally good guy.
Wade Brown: You don't think he's a serial killer or anything?
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you again, Tortle, wearing the staff of Meril, you know, Valphine in her white armor, and glowing eyes, and Halberd in his… a Brewbarry with his halberd, and looks to go, well,
Kostadis Roussos: Should I be worried?
Wade Brown: You never know with these types. You never know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Gary Young: I'd be worried about him.
Wade Brown: I think we can let Uncle Tom off the hook, and
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so Uncle Tom's kind of like, you know, I just… I just want you to know, I mean, we're always… and… and when you… if you've got… now that I know… pauses, he's trying to, like, really hard. So…
Kostadis Roussos: So, Soma, right? You introduced yourself at some.
Wade Brown: Yes, I, yes, I definitely did.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Soma, look, now that I know that turtles are looking for housing, perhaps you could tell me, like, what makes a good turtle room?
Wade Brown: Oh, a nice hearth, you know, plenty of water. Usually near, you know, near a body of water is nice.
David Mendenhall: All turtles are the same, right?
Wade Brown: Yes, we… I speak for all turtles. I'm the Jesse Jackson of turtles.
Kostadis Roussos: I was giving you an opportunity to troll the guy, but Soma doesn't troll.
Wade Brown: No, SOMA does not.
Kostadis Roussos: Silva does not. Alright.
Wade Brown: So, so must Ernest.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, so, a few hours later, he wakes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Wade Brown: And I assume I have to recast my rat at some point, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: I don't think it lasts forever, let me just burn another slot…
David Mendenhall: You guys are just giving me updates on the sending, so at this point, I should probably join you, right? It's been a few hours.
Wade Brown: Yeah, yeah, we can have you come along.
David Mendenhall: I probably am with you now.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I can tell you about Denvar.
David Mendenhall: Why don't I tell you about, the local were-rat mafia.
Wade Brown: Yeah, there's were-rats all over, isn't it?
Wade Brown: I expect them to be such a big player.
David Mendenhall: We just gotta clear out these spiders, and it's more money for the studio. This is great. Finally a business opportunity.
David Mendenhall: Fair Trade Gold.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, now I know. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you show up, And,
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you, you, you, you go to the, the stone… he goes to a stone wall.
Kostadis Roussos: He opens up, and you see that he looks around, trying to be as discreet as possible.
David Mendenhall: It's a dead drop.
Kostadis Roussos: it picks up
Kostadis Roussos: He picks up, he opens a… he opens a… pulls a stone, and he grabs a bag, and he closes the bag.
Wade Brown: Just a bare stone wall, like, on the edge of the…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, it's a… it's a… it's a stone that… it's,
Kostadis Roussos: it backs into a building, right? So it's like… right? And so it backs into a building.
David Mendenhall: Is it like a two-way… it's like…
David Mendenhall: like a doctor's office window, right? Like, where, like, you put it in on one side and close the door, and then they…
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, you'd have to go.
David Mendenhall: We'd have to go inspect it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'd have to go inspect it.
David Mendenhall: Alright, well, it's… yeah. I mean, it's effectively a dead drop, so, like, we should let him go and just inspect at this point.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Wade Brown: Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean…
Wade Brown: Barring coming back the next evening before he leaves his house, but we don't know exactly how early he has to leave to make these drops, so…
Wade Brown: It's probably a… Denvar might be a dead end.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go.
Wade Brown: eyeball the wall.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you go to the wall, right?
David Mendenhall: Valphine, you wanna do your…
Wade Brown: Infinite perception.
David Mendenhall: Mmm.
Gary Young: You mean, like, on him, or on the…
David Mendenhall: on the wall.
Wade Brown: on the wall.
Gary Young: I'm gonna look at him just before he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: He's, he looks at the, shit.
Kostadis Roussos: And he, he smiles.
Gary Young: Please, please.
David Mendenhall: Got it.
Gary Young: Okay.
Gary Young: Yeah, that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: Who got us money.
Wade Brown: Payday! I'm going to the casino!
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. I…
Gary Young: Could take a little look, then, at the rock.
Kostadis Roussos: What you notice is that the rock I mean…
Kostadis Roussos: basically, it's a two-way rock, right? Somebody… you don't know if the person who puts it in was on the other side of the rock, or on this side… it was in the house, or not in the house, so you'd have to go into the house to check it out.
Gary Young: Oh, okay. Well, let's loop around.
Wade Brown: Don't tell me it's hospital.
David Mendenhall: Or is it Earth, or…
Kostadis Roussos: It's a stone indwelling.
David Mendenhall: the stone dwelling.
Kostadis Roussos: It's right, you know, Built out of stone.
David Mendenhall: Trying to think if we have a… somewhere… something that can help us without going into the house.
Wade Brown: I mean, we have mold earth, but I know you won't.
David Mendenhall: It's not earth, it's stone.
Gary Young: Let's just quickly look around the house and see what it is.
Wade Brown: I mean, it's clearly, it's gotta be.
David Mendenhall: The outside of the house.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it's gotta be a Margaster ride residence, or something like that.
Gary Young: It's not a residence, it's not a shop.
Wade Brown: You don't think?
Gary Young: That's what I'm questioning. Is it a residence or a shop?
Kostadis Roussos: Give me one second. I'm on the fly coming up with this shit.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So I need to make up my mind.
Wade Brown: You didn't plan for this eventuality?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
Wade Brown: Teasing.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: As you walk around, you realize that the house you've landed on is a… it's actually a tavern.
Gary Young: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: The House of a Thousand Faces.
David Mendenhall: So many taverns. Well, maybe we can just walk right in. Are they open?
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: It is early in the morning, but no, they are, in fact, open.
Wade Brown: I mean, somebody's obviously in there paying off, shady debts.
Kostadis Roussos: Correct.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Okay. Yeah, sure, we can hit the tavern. I mean, it's early, but why not?
Kostadis Roussos: It's 5 o'clock.
Wade Brown: clock somewhere.
David Mendenhall: Sure, Brewbarry's all for it.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I just, what did I call it? I gave it a name.
Wade Brown: The House of a Thousand Faces.
Kostadis Roussos: The House of a Thousand Faces.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just, make sure it's not hidden, right? Alright, the house of a Thousand Faces, there we go.
David Mendenhall: Oh, so I… okay, so I do have an idea of how we can investigate this without going inside, which is the knock spell.
David Mendenhall: So we could open our side, and we can cast Knock on the other side.
David Mendenhall: Do you want to try to do that, or do you want to just go inside the tavern?
Wade Brown: I assume Soma would just go inside, she's not exactly, magic wielder.
Wade Brown: Or familiar with all of that.
Wade Brown: Sorry, how does… you use NOC to open up the two-way, the dead drop stuff, or what?
David Mendenhall: Yeah, like… Right, we can't open the other side of the…
David Mendenhall: We can't physically open the other side of the… of the two-way…
David Mendenhall: hole, but we could… I think we could magically open it if we wanted to do that.
Wade Brown: I mean, if you… if you propose that, yeah, I think that's, worth a shot.
David Mendenhall: And then we could look in and see, like, what room are we looking at, try to find the right room, or we could even send one of your rats in there to look around.
Wade Brown: I like that combo.
Gary Young: I have a different strategy, which is, we go in there and offer them a business proposal.
Wade Brown: Yeah, Vukradin could play.
Gary Young: your booking agency.
Wade Brown: Actually, you know, getting backstage in there would,
Wade Brown: You know, you'd have access to staff-only areas where you could, you know, do your music prep, and by music prep.
Gary Young: There you go.
David Mendenhall: We could cast two spells, or we could have an…
Wade Brown: Or we can get paid!
David Mendenhall: extended contract process, and several performance roles, and hours of time.
David Mendenhall: I do like to perform, though.
Wade Brown: Yeah, see, I mean… These are tough choices.
David Mendenhall: involved.
Wade Brown: Let's do both!
David Mendenhall: ball.
Wade Brown: Porque no los dos.
David Mendenhall: Exactly. Why not?
Wade Brown: I'll fire off another… well, I guess the ride's still fine.
David Mendenhall: I'll have to ask the DM if it works, but the idea is that we open our side of the hole, we cast knock on the other side of the hole, hopefully opening it, and then send…
David Mendenhall: Send the rat, the familiar rat, through to look around on what… the room on the other side.
David Mendenhall: Did you get all that?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I did, okay.
Gary Young: It's a simple strategy.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, that's what you're doing. What are the other… what is everybody else doing? Are you all, like, doing that together?
David Mendenhall: Before we go inside. We're all together.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we want to at least not walk in completely blind.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Wade Brown: runs off and gets, you know, just goes in and orders beer without waiting for us, but I don't know.
Gary Young: Very taverned? Okay. Yeah, I don't.
Wade Brown: I don't think we could…
David Mendenhall: We're gonna walk into the tavern. The rest of us are trying to solve the puzzle.
Kostadis Roussos: Brewbarry's already in the tavern.
Wade Brown: Yeah, he was born in the town.
David Mendenhall: He's down, he's… he's…
Kostadis Roussos: Actually.
David Mendenhall: Zen at this point.
Kostadis Roussos: Actually, to be fair, Brewbarry has heard about this tavern for some time.
Kostadis Roussos: And when he was first in Neverwinter, he could never get there because he never had the money.
David Mendenhall: Oh, there you go.
David Mendenhall: Right. It's more of a high-end establishment.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. He was warm.
David Mendenhall: a Common Chord slum, and this was a high-end establishment.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I mean, you know… And, and he… I think he'd heard about this place.
Wade Brown: He's a man of class now, he can buy his way into high society.
David Mendenhall: I do have one question about our fame, though. Sorry, this is a little bit off-topic, but, like, do we know how we became so famous? Or is that a mystery for us to be solving?
Kostadis Roussos: You do not know how you became…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I thought so, okay.
Gary Young: Isn't it obvious? It's the… it's the quality of your… your… your talent.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: not.
Gary Young: It's totally not, you sure.
David Mendenhall: It definitely is not.
Wade Brown: But of course, the naivety…
David Mendenhall: There is a force behind the fame that is.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
David Mendenhall: some… Groups are maneuvering.
David Mendenhall: We're being…
Wade Brown: manipulated.
David Mendenhall: advantage for some reason.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, okay, so, you send in the rat, the rat, like, sneaks around.
Wade Brown: So NOC does work on the stone wall thing? Okay.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: it, it does work on it. And,
Kostadis Roussos: As the rat is looking around, you realize that this is the back office of the… it looks like a back office, no windows, no nothing. You… the rat looks around and notices
Kostadis Roussos: a symbol of the Harpers. So this is a Harper…
David Mendenhall: Harp?
Wade Brown: Oh, wow!
David Mendenhall: Okay, so is it, like, a storage room, or, like, what other…
Kostadis Roussos: And off a backup, back of, like, you know, think of a spike… Desk. Yeah, desk. Papers, kind of things like that.
David Mendenhall: desk, papers, supplies?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you wouldn't steal anything, so yeah.
David Mendenhall: No, no, it's just a rat.
Wade Brown: No, they're right, I can't carry anything.
Kostadis Roussos: that Vukradin wouldn't steal anything.
David Mendenhall: No.
Wade Brown: No, no, he's a man.
David Mendenhall: Definitely wouldn't steal anything.
Kostadis Roussos: I know, just every time I… with other parties, I have to be thoughtful, because, like, the next thing is they're gonna go steal everything.
Wade Brown: He can't see what the rat's doing, though. He only has to trust, you know, my word for it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, sorry. But no, it looks like, you know, HQ for the Harpers, the local Harpers.
Wade Brown: Harper, so that's… Weird.
Wade Brown: The Harpers are… smuggling?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the Harpers aren't… are the Harpers smuggling, or they're arranging for that 9th crate?
Wade Brown: Well, I mean, clearly that 9th grade is some amount of smuggling, because it's being, you know…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I'm good.
Wade Brown: directly delivered, so yes, the Harpers are smuggling in some capacity.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Oh, just… I just want to remind you, the Harpers in my campaign world are not good people.
Kostadis Roussos: I assume.
Wade Brown: Oh, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no… the only good people are the Order of the Gauntlet.
Wade Brown: Debatable.
Gary Young: Are there?
Kostadis Roussos: You know, they are.
David Mendenhall: Reformed. They're reformed.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
David Mendenhall: Well, they had that whole thing with the barbarians, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that was… they were misled by their political masters.
David Mendenhall: Exactly, that's what I'm saying. They've been past that, they're reformed now.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, and so they've now rejected those political masters.
David Mendenhall: Basically, they're the Reformed order of the Gauntlet.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and they recognized that they were used by powerful forces, and now they're all about, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: The little guy.
Wade Brown: Truth, justice, and the American Way.
Kostadis Roussos: Different comic book. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
David Mendenhall: It's 10.30.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, just to give you guys. So it's a comfortable tavern, it's got mirrors and mannequins and antiquated fashions, lush couches.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: Who puts Mattel?
Wade Brown: Raken's in it, anyway.
Kostadis Roussos: Lush couches, a fire that actually draws…
Kostadis Roussos: You know, it's kind of like a high-end place, and the Bluelake District is sort of a low-end place.
Kostadis Roussos: Makes sense.
Kostadis Roussos: Then mixed note, there's something off about it.
Kostadis Roussos: And as for the… where the rat was, it wasn't in the first floor, but it kind of went…
Kostadis Roussos: Anyway, it was… And, yes, it was the…
David Mendenhall: level.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the basement level.
David Mendenhall: Basement model.
Wade Brown: Went down, alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright? Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Brewbarry… Brewbarry walks in, and, we'll just…
Kostadis Roussos: You guys know that it's a Harper.
Wade Brown: Yep, it's a good place, I need to leave it.
Kostadis Roussos: It's as good a place as any place to leave it, so you've arrived in the Harper establishment in the Bluelake District.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: And I guess… and we have the information so that at any time we can go face
David Mendenhall: This spider infestation.
David Mendenhall: In the sewers, and try to clear it out.
David Mendenhall: For the… the were-rat Mafia?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you have to go and find the Weird Rat Mafia again, yes.
David Mendenhall: well, we talked to them, and we agreed we'd do this job for them, so I'm assuming they gave us the necessary information to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, they… yes, they did. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Cool.
David Mendenhall: Maybe we could do that next time. We haven't had a combat in, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I know, I was… I had, I had.
David Mendenhall: It's been, like, 3 months since we had a combat.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, I had, like, 3 combats set up, but, like, you guys went in a different direction.
Gary Young: It's a lot of girls.
David Mendenhall: spells, though.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Kostadis Roussos: What'd you say, Gary?
Gary Young: We went to left field.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you went into left field, but it's okay. Okay, so the House of a Thousand Faces.
Wade Brown: I got to third base.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You went through the sewers over here. I just need to put a… I need to put a marker saying there's a sewer entrance over here.
Kostadis Roussos: For entrance, so I don't… I don't forget.
Kostadis Roussos: Sure, sure.
Wade Brown: You won't forget.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, sewer entries. Alright, so,
Kostadis Roussos: You, the party, is at the House of the Thousand Faces, and we will continue next week.
Wade Brown: Have a good week, y'all.
Kostadis Roussos: Have a good week. I had fun today, I hope you guys did.
Wade Brown: Oh, that's fun.
David Mendenhall: Bye-bye.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, man. Take care.